Oh hello again
О привет снова
[ __ ] that you merged sense merged you
жопик что ты слился смысле слился ты же
ran away look at the record and didn’t
убежал то что посмотри запись так и не
answer Look at the answer how the
ответил Посмотри заответствие как
fool put on a hat come on come on
дурачок шапочку одел давай давай
You’re
Ты
even afraid to
даже боишься
scratch your mouth it won’t work Tell me
чесать свою ртом не получится Расскажи С
which Mariupol you ran away from, well, let’s
какого Мариуполя ты убежал это ну давай
deceive, why are you there  refugee what
обманываешь да что ты там беженец что
is Zugres beach Tell me how, uh, how
такое пляж Зугрэсе Расскажи как э-э как
do you feel about the fact that Medvedchuk was
ты относишься к тому что медведчука
liberated Russia did not understand
освободила Россия не понял
[music]
[музыка]
defended Mariupol, who ran away
обороняли Мариуполь который вот убежал
here you are now I will go like you now
вот ты сейчас я пойду как ты сейчас
When you learn to communicate come the
Когда научишься общаться приходи
feeling that when a sheep was
ощущение от того что когда на овца
exchanged for
обменяли на медлячках которые Мариуполе
[Laughter]
сидели
Bingo
Бинго
Hey brother Where is yours Where is
Эй братишка Где твоя Где шапочка
Sharikov's hat
Шарикова
Damn, I'm shorter than God That is, the glass of
Блин я божнее короче То есть стекло
grandfather while they shmaly there where there is some
дедушку пока шмали там куда там какой-то
Dude you look you said that in
Чувак ты смотрю ты же рассказывал что
short the
короче
Nazis tried there yesterday Putin gave
нацисты там пытались вчера Путин отдал
these Nazis back to Ukraine  back on the
этих нацистов в Украину назад назад на
way to this for Medvedchuk I exchanged
путь на это на медведчука Обменял
and how all these Russian brothers
и как все эти российские братушки
Ivanushki until it turns out to be stuffy
Иванушки до получается духли
to make it
чтобы короче
shorter  ocsify yes these Azov people And
деноцифицировать да этих азовцев А
now they were sent back to Ukraine as part of the denocification
теперь их в рамках деноцификации отдали
so that the new Vanyushki would go to
назад в Украину чтобы новые Ванюшки шли
liberate Ukraine from these Azov people,
освобождать Украину от вот этих азовцев
this is a Vicious circle and the
это Замкнутый круг и
guys Yes, everyone who watches These are
ребятки Да все которые смотрят Вот таких
clowns who collects donatters
клоунов до который собирает донаттерс
like Help a refugee from Mariupol, a
как Помогите беженцу из Мариуполя
survivor in this hell Yes  a dude from dodged
выживший в этом аду Да чувак с петляла
from Mariupol when he lives somewhere in the
из Мариуполя когда там где-то живет в
Rostov region there is still figs how
Ростовской области там еще фиг насколько
old he was just born a long time ago now he
лет так он просто родился давно теперь
tells you that in short I
вам рассказывает что короче я
am a refugee refugees from Mariupol to
беженецкого беженцы из Мариуполя до
real refugees before who fled both to the
реальный беженцы до которые бежали и на
territory of Ukraine and to the territory of
территорию Украины и на территорию
Russia here they are  they really need help for
России вот им действительно нужно помощь
such a shorter clown who sits and
они такому клоуну короче который сидит и
just stupidly deceives why
просто просто тупо обманывается почему
he merged again Because there is nothing to
он снова слился Потому что нечего
say if he was so
сказать если он так
worried about Mariupol Yes, in short, the
переживал за Мариуполь Да короче
Azov creatures sat on the Nazis, so
азовские твари сидели на застали так вот
yesterday Putin
вчера Путин этих азовских тварей
turned out to exchange these Azov creatures for the Hero of Russia a bear
получается Обменял на Героя России
or  not a Hero of Russia, but who will explain to me
или не Героя России а кто мне объяснит
Yes,
Да
Russians And for  that you will die in Ukraine for
русские А за что вы дохнете в Украине за
Putin to decide some of your interests before
Путин решал какие-то свои интересы до
someone took Medvedchuk And the children are all
кого-то медведчука забрал А дети все
Vanka from Buryatia there Dagestan is shorter
Ваньки из Бурятии там Дагестана короче
Moscow region direct Cape Glory to Ukraine
Подмосковье прямая Мыса Слава Украине
subscribe to the
подписывайтесь на канал
channel like the comments maybe the video
ставим лайк коментарии может быть видео
took off and smear
взлетала так и смажем
[music  ]
[музыка]
there is no fate in Telegram
в Telegram нет
In short, you will
судьба Короче ты будешь на меня
fall for me, you will be undermined by
попадаться у тебя будет подрываться
Fart just from one of my views,
Пукан просто от одного моего вида
how we drove this one is coming
как мы загнали этого грядим
dodik type who says that he is
додика типа который рассказывает что он
like a refugee in Mariupol and this is
как бы беженец Мариуполе и вот это
collecting money deceiving suckers in Russia
собирает бабки обманывает лохов в России
This is how we should C  every Russian or
Вот так мы должны С каждым руссочком или
they should see
они должны видеть
everyone just awesome the
всем просто офигенней
fourth time you see it's fate fate
четвёртый раз видишь это судьба судьба
brings together you can't run away that you can't run away there
сводит это не убежишь что там не убежишь
Yes look at the question no
Да смотри на вопрос нет опять таратория
again chattering but ask again because you were
но опять напросить потому что
exchanged for a Medvedchuk
обменяли на медведчука
then look then if you will just
тогда смотри тогда если ты будешь просто
chat
забалтывать
then by your birthday  since you are such a
тогда к дню рождения раз ты такой
popular blogger Yes, you posted me there
популярный блогер Да ты меня выложил там
Come on, here you are, September 26 is my
Давай ты вот у меня 26 сентября день
birthday  let me at least donate 100 thousand
рождения давайте мне тысяч 100 хотя бы
then we’ll talk
задонать тогда мы с тобой поговорим
normally only you won’t interrupt
нормально Только ты не будешь перебивать
I would answer your question Well you don’t
я ответил бы тебя на вопрос Ну ты же не
know how, you don’t know how, you’re so
умеешь понимаешь не умеешь ты такая
dear Well, you see Yes, that’s it
дорогая Ну вот видишь Да вот всё
, happy birthday, in fact, you said that
с днём рождения по факту ты говорил что
the creatures
твари
answered the question when you will prepare
ответил на вопрос когда ты подготовишься
nothing just about the
ничего просто по поводу дугресса По
dugress About all these bastards
поводу По поводу всех этих [__]
who killed for 8 years you will teach eight
которые убивали 8 лет восемь научишь
they sent to Ukraine and when will you
отдали в Украину и когда ли в Украину
get back to Ukraine You will type how it happened that
наберешь Наберешь как так получилось что
fate is fate
судьба судьба
and then you know when
и тут знаешь когда
I was already tortured to comment on it
я уже замучился его комментировать
In short, the dude gets again
Короче чувак попадает снова
shorter in chat roulette, you
короче в чат рулетке сидит какой-то
know, you know, the admin panel is just bantering from him
знаешь админку просто уже с него стебет
As soon as a
Как только можно
fire occurs Damn, I don’t know for
возгорание происходит Блин я не знаю за
today I’ve got three Third Time,
сегодня это у меня три Третий Раз
it’s just
попался так же так
as easy Write in the comments like
уже просто Напишите в комментариях типа
jumping up shorter laugh Everything  Glory to
навскикаться короче ржать Всё Слава
Ukraine, pedantic Russian bloggers
Украине педроватый русских блогеров
Grishchenko Dmitry Romanovich today you
Грищенко Дмитрий Романович сегодня Вам
are 28 years old and the military commissariat
исполнилось 28 лет и военный комиссариат
Ro  Andrey Vasilyevich’s attempt and now roulette invites you to defend mother Russia against NATO of the malicious military commissariat of Rostov in the region, by order of the Ukrainian
Ростовской области по заказу Укра
Nazi, the attempt of Andrey Vasilyevich and
нациста попытка Андрея Васильевича и
now roulette invites you to stand up for
сейчас рулетки приглашает вас встать на
mother Russia against NATO, the
оборону России матушке против НАТО
Rostov
злостного военный комиссариат Ростов в
region expresses its deep gratitude to the
области выражает огромную благодарность
blogger of the priests Kondri Vasilyevich for his
блогеру попы кондри Васильевичу за
assistance in compiling a list of
содействие в формировании списка
bloggers supporting the z-operation and
поддерживающих z-операцию блогеров и
sending them to
отправки их на
support units  of the Russian army, all those
поддержку частей российской армии все те
who supported the z-operation for 7 months and
кто 7 месяцев поддерживал z-операцию и
support mobilization should be in the
поддерживает мобилизацию должны в первых
forefront by their example to show other
рядах своим примером показать другим
citizens of the Russian Federation How to
гражданам Российской Федерации Как нужно
defend the Motherland, the war will end
защищать Родину война закончится тогда
when all Russian propagandists
когда все российские пропагандисты
are at the front Citizens of the Russian
окажутся на фронте Граждане Российской
Federation The Ministry of Defense urges
Федерации Министерство обороны призывает
you not to sit idly by  in this difficult time
вас не сидеть сложа руки в это сложное
for the fatherland, we can form lists of
для отечества время формировать списки
people supporting the public Z
людей поддерживающих публичный Z
operation and transfer them to the military
операцию и передавать их военные
commissariats of your region
комиссариаты вашего региона мы можем
together with the motherland
Родине вместе